slowly.
ゆっくり
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Can I ask you to stop?
止まってもらっていいですか?
that's right.
そうです
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
Look here.
こっち見て
This way.
こっちよ
A face appeared in the front.
前面に顔が出てきました
Your face is looking at me.
顔がこっち見てるよ
Yeah.
うん
First, close your mouth.
まず口を閉じて
Try your best to put it in your mouth.
口の中に頑張って入れて
It's amazing because I felt real today.
すごい今日イリアルしたからです
I was so frustrated.
めっちゃ悔しかった
Was it frustrating?
悔しかった?
It was frustrating.
悔しかった
Seishi.
せいし
It was frustrating.
悔しかった
painful?
苦しい?
What, what does it hurt?
何、何苦しいですか?
Is it a hoax?
嘘騒ぎですか?
It was painful.
苦しかった
It's painful, isn't it?
苦しいでしょ
painful?
苦しい?
The one who went to Kyoto, America.
アメリカ京都行ったやつだ
photograph?
撮影?
It would be painful if I were to get hit.
おなけ絶対打てたら苦しいでしょ
Oh, filler?
あ、フィラーを?
No, it's not like that, it started getting creepy even before that.
いや違う、その前からなんかさ、不気味になったからさ
I seemed to know.
知らそうでした
Wha-wha, something happened?
な、な、何かあった?
Yeah.
うん
Tell me where.
どこか教えてよ
I feel like I'm sorry,
なんか、申し訳なかったっていうのがさ、
I was wondering why so many things had disappeared.
なんか、 なんでこんなに消えてんだろうなって思ったのさ
Even before shooting.
撮影前から